cheatcodesweb.com 2008-12-17

# Privacy Policy - Cheat Codes Web

**Home  >  Privacy Policy**

We want our users to always be aware of any information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

**Information collection and use**

For each visit to our website, our web server automatically recognizes only the visitors IP (Internet Protocol) address, but not the email address. This can reveal the identity of your Internet Service Provider, and their local point-of-presence. This information is only used  for general traffic tracking and security.

Email addresses are collected if visitors subscribe our Cheats Alert Newsletter. Email addresses are then only used by Cheat Codes Web and not sold, rented, given, or shown to any other company for any use whatsoever. Our use of email addresses is to notify visitors of new cheats added to the site.

All subscribers always have an option to unsubscribe at any time. Our newsletter is double opt-in, meaning subscribers must confirm their desire to be on the list by clicking a link in an email sent to their sign up address. This is done to protect all email addresses from being mistakenly or fraudulently added to our list by 3rd parties.

**Special Notification with respect to Children's Privacy**

In response to concerns about protecting children's privacy online, Congress enacted the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 ("COPPA"), which sets forth rules and procedures governing the ways in which Web sites may collect, use and disclose any personal information for children under the age of 13. In accordance with our policy and COPPA regulations, we DO NOT:

  1. Request or knowingly collect personally identifiable online or offline contact information from users under 13 years of age;

  2. Knowingly use or share personal information from users under 13 years of age with third parties;

  3. Give children the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information;

  4. Entice children with the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity.

**Third Party Advertising**

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by third-party advertising. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. 

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Our third-party advertiser may use cookies on this site to limit the number and frequency of various ads displayed as you browse the site.  
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that use if you desire.

**Notification of changes**

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement.
